{
  "flashards" : [ {
    "question" : "あ",
    "answer" : "a",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "い",
    "answer" : "i",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "う",
    "answer" : "u",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "え",
    "answer" : "e",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "お",
    "answer" : "o",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "か",
    "answer" : "ka",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "き",
    "answer" : "ki",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "く",
    "answer" : "ku",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "け",
    "answer" : "ke",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "こ",
    "answer" : "ko",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "さ",
    "answer" : "sa",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "し",
    "answer" : "shi",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "す",
    "answer" : "su",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "せ",
    "answer" : "se",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "そ",
    "answer" : "so",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "た",
    "answer" : "ta",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ち",
    "answer" : "chi",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "つ",
    "answer" : "tsu",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "て",
    "answer" : "te",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "と",
    "answer" : "to",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "な",
    "answer" : "na",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "に",
    "answer" : "ni",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ぬ",
    "answer" : "nu",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ね",
    "answer" : "ne",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "の",
    "answer" : "no",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "は",
    "answer" : "ha",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ひ",
    "answer" : "hi",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ふ",
    "answer" : "fu",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "へ",
    "answer" : "he",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ほ",
    "answer" : "ho",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ま",
    "answer" : "ma",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "み",
    "answer" : "mi",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "む",
    "answer" : "mu",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "め",
    "answer" : "me",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "も",
    "answer" : "mo",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "や",
    "answer" : "ya",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ゆ",
    "answer" : "yu",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "よ",
    "answer" : "yo",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ら",
    "answer" : "ra",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "り",
    "answer" : "ri",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "る",
    "answer" : "ru",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "れ",
    "answer" : "re",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ろ",
    "answer" : "ro",
    "tagged" : []
  },{
    "question" : "わ",
    "answer" : "wa",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "を",
    "answer" : "wo",
    "tagged" : []
  }, {
    "question" : "ん",
    "answer" : "n",
    "tagged" : []
  }]
}